https://ktena.com.au/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Ktena Knitting Mills
Skip to content
We are manufacturing Washable Medical Isolation Gowns - Bulk Orders - Contact Us
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the privacy policy pertaining to this Site: www.ktena.com, www.ktena.com.au, www.merinoskins.com.au and all sites of the affiliates of Ktena Knitting Pty Ltd (“Ktena”) which are linked to this Site (collectively, the “Sites”). By using any Site, you are agreeing to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement. For other terms and conditions that apply to your use of the Sites, please review our Legal Statement.
For purposes of this Privacy Policy Statement, “Personal Information” means any information by which you can be personally identified, and includes your name, your address, your telephone number, your e-mail address and the like. Most Sites do not require that you submit Personal Information to Ktena. However, some Sites may request Personal Information in order to help Ktena serve you more effectively. Ktena collects Personal Information only when you voluntarily submit such Personal Information to us, such as when placing a product order through a Site.
For each visitor to the Sites, our web servers automatically recognize only information regarding the visitor’s domain name (or that of the visitor’s access provider) and e-mail address. Regardless of the purpose for which it is submitted, it is Ktena’s policy to maintain all Personal Information as confidential, and to use such Personal Information only for the following purposes:
• for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered (for example, to complete a product purchase etc.);
• to improve the content, appearance and utility of the Sites;
• to track our visitors’ use of the Sites for internal market research; and
• to notify our visitors of updates to the Sites.
It is Ktena’s policy to keep Personal Information only for so long as needed for such purposes. At any time, you may obtain a summary of the Personal Information on record with Ktena which has been collected about you via this Site. Except for Personal Information we need to complete your purchase of products, you may request at any time that Ktena dispose of any or all Personal Information about you. In addition, at any time you may request: (i) that Ktena correct any such Personal Information; or (ii) [that such Personal Information not be provided to third parties; or (iii)] that such Personal Information be removed from Ktena’s marketing databases. To make any request described above, send an e-mail to admins@ktena.com.au.
When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact e-mail address, name, address and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly.
Ktena reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy Statement at any time. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy Statement will mean that you accept those changes.
Get In Touch! Ktena Knitting Mills
20 Burlington Street,
Oakleigh,
Victoria 3166
Australia
Phone 1300 583 622
Wool ProductsLadies Thermo Fleece®
Mens Thermo Fleece®
Unisex Merino Skins®
Additional ResourcesAbout Ktena
Contact Us
Factory Shop
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
Size Charts
Warranty and Returns
About Us Ktena Knitting Mills is a leading Australian thermal underwear manufacturer that has proudly contributed in revolutionising the concept of thermal underwear.
Follow us on our Facebook page.
Follow us on our Instagram page.
© 2020 Ktena Knitting Pty Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
